[
  {
    "question": "What shall be the minimum volume in cubic inches for an 8 AWG conductor in a box?",
    "choices": ["2.50 in", "4.25 in", "3.00 in", "1.75 in"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3905.12.2.1",
    "correct_answer": "3.00 in"
  },
  {
    "question": "At least one outlet in bathrooms is required to be within what dimension of each lavatory basin?",
    "choices": ["34 in", "36 in", "32 in", "30 in"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3901.6",
    "correct_answer": "36 in"
  },
  {
    "question": "A receptacle for a cord-and-plug-connected range hood shall be supplied by an individual branch circuit?",
    "choices": ["True", "False"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 4101.3",
    "correct_answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Direct buried conductors and cables emerging from the ground shall be protected to a point at least how far above finished grade?",
    "choices": ["8 ft", "6 ft", "7 ft", "4 ft"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3803.3",
    "correct_answer": "8 ft"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shall be the minimum burial depth of direct burial cables or conductors in locations not specifically identified?",
    "choices": ["24 in", "18 in", "16 in", "12 in"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3803.1",
    "correct_answer": "24 in"
  },
  {
    "question": "Electric spa and hot tub water heaters shall be listed and shall have the heating elements subdivided into loads not exceeding ______ amperes?",
    "choices": ["55", "60", "48", "24"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 4208.2",
    "correct_answer": "48"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shall be the minimum cover for rigid metal conduit installed under a driveway?",
    "choices": ["36 in", "12 in", "24 in", "6 in"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3803.1",
    "correct_answer": "24 in"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where a branch circuit or a feeder supplies a continuous load it shall have an allowable ampacity equal to or greater than the non-continuous load plus ______ percent of continuous load?",
    "choices": ["125", "200", "150", "100"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3701.2.1",
    "correct_answer": "125"
  },
  {
    "question": "Switches shall not be more than what dimension above a floor or working platform, when in its highest position?",
    "choices": ["6 ft 7 in", "3 ft 7 in", "6 ft 10 in", "10 ft 9 in"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 4001.6",
    "correct_answer": "6 ft 7 in"
  },
  {
    "question": "Above-ground service-entrance cables subject to physical damage shall be protected by what schedule PVC conduit?",
    "choices": ["40", "90", "60", "80"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3605.5",
    "correct_answer": "80"
  },
  {
    "question": "The minimum headroom for working spaces for service equipment and panel boards shall be how many feet?",
    "choices": ["6 1/4 ft", "6 ft", "7 1/2 ft", "6 1/2 ft"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3405.2",
    "correct_answer": "6 1/2 ft"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shall be the minimum AWG size copper grounding electrode conductor when the largest ungrounded service entrance conductor for a panel is 1/0 copper?",
    "choices": ["6 AWG", "4 AWG", "8 AWG", "1/0 AWG"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3603.4",
    "correct_answer": "6 AWG"
  },
  {
    "question": "All circuit conductors between the service equipment, or the source of a separately derived system, or other power supply source and the final branch-circuit overcurrent device.",
    "choices": ["Service conductors", "Service cables", "Feeder", "Circuit"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 35",
    "correct_answer": "Feeder"
  },
  {
    "question": "Flexible cords for kitchen range hoods shall have what minimum and maximum length?",
    "choices": ["18 in to 48 in", "12 in to 42 in", "20 in to 40 in", "30 in to 36 in"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 4101.3",
    "correct_answer": "18 in to 48 in"
  },
  {
    "question": "Outdoor receptacles that are not readily accessible and are supplied from a dedicated branch circuit for electric snow-melting or deicing equipment shall be permitted to be installed without ground-fault circuit-interrupter protection for personnel?",
    "choices": ["True", "False"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 4101.7",
    "correct_answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unused cable and raceway openings in cabinets and panel boards shall be effectively ______ to afford protection equivalent to that of the wall cabinet?",
    "choices": ["Open", "Closed", "Labeled", "Marked"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3404.6",
    "correct_answer": "Closed"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many 15 or 20 amp receptacles supplied by a general purpose branch circuit shall be located a minimum of 6 feet from and not more than 20 feet from the inside walls of pools?",
    "choices": ["4", "3", "2", "1"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 4203.1.3",
    "correct_answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "A luminaire that weighs more than ______ or exceeds 16 inches in any dimension shall not be supported by the screws of a lamp holder?",
    "choices": ["12 Lbs", "5 Lbs", "6 Lbs", "15 Lbs"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 4004.4",
    "correct_answer": "6 Lbs"
  },
  {
    "question": "Underground service laterals that are not encased in concrete and that are buried 18 inches or more below grade shall have their location identified by what?",
    "choices": ["Warning Ribbon", "Tracer wire", "Metal tags", "Not required"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3803.2",
    "correct_answer": "Warning Ribbon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Recessed incandescent fixtures shall have what kind of protection?",
    "choices": ["Overcurrent", "Thermal", "Heat", "Cold"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 4003.6",
    "correct_answer": "Thermal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where raceways are installed in wet locations above grade, the interior of such raceways shall be considered to be a ______ location.",
    "choices": ["Hazardous", "Wet", "Damp", "Sealed"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3802.8",
    "correct_answer": "Wet"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where installed in raceways, conductors of what size AWG and larger shall be stranded?",
    "choices": ["6", "8", "2", "4"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3406.4",
    "correct_answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Threaded bonding connections at a service shall be fastened how tight?",
    "choices": ["Wrench tight", "40 lb ft of torque", "20 lb ft of torque", "15 lb ft of torque"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3609.4.2",
    "correct_answer": "Wrench tight"
  },
  {
    "question": "Flexible cords for kitchen waste disposals shall be what dimension?",
    "choices": ["12 in to 36 in", "12 in to 30 in", "16 in to 30 in", "18 in to 36 in"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 4101.3",
    "correct_answer": "18 in to 36 in"
  },
  {
    "question": "All 15 and 20 amp, single phase, 125-volt receptacles located within ______ feet of the inside walls of pools and outdoor spas and hot tubs shall be protected by a Class A ground-fault circuit-interrupter?",
    "choices": ["10", "15", "20", "25"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 4203.1.4",
    "correct_answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where used outside, aluminum or copper-clad aluminum grounding conductors shall not be terminated within ______ inches of the earth?",
    "choices": ["12 in", "18 in", "6 in", "8 in"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3610.2 (3)",
    "correct_answer": "18 in"
  },
  {
    "question": "Generally, ceiling suspended paddle fans shall be supported independently of outlet boxes when weighing over 50 lbs?",
    "choices": ["True", "False"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3905.6.2",
    "correct_answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "A minimum of one ___ -ampere-rated branch circuit shall be provided for receptacles located in the laundry area and shall serve only receptacle outlets in the laundry area.",
    "choices": ["20 amp", "40 amp", "15 amp", "30 amp"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3703.3",
    "correct_answer": "20 amp"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cords that supply swimming pool equipment shall have a copper equipment grounding conductor not smaller than what AWG?",
    "choices": ["12", "13", "14", "18"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 4202.3 (1)",
    "correct_answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "For one-family dwellings, the rating of the ungrounded conductors shall be not less than how many amperes three wire?",
    "choices": ["150", "200", "100", "1000"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3602.1",
    "correct_answer": "100"
  },
  {
    "question": "All parts of a pool required to be bonded shall be bonded together with a copper conductor not smaller than what AWG?",
    "choices": ["6", "8", "10", "12"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 4204.2",
    "correct_answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "The underground service conductors between the electric utility supply system and the service point.",
    "choices": ["Service feeder", "Feeder", "Service lateral", "Service drop"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 35",
    "correct_answer": "Service lateral"
  },
  {
    "question": "A branch circuit using 14 AWG conductors and a 15 Ampere overcurrent-protection device shall have a maximum load rating of how many amps?",
    "choices": ["15 amps", "18 amps", "16.5 amps", "15.5 amps"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3702.15 (1)",
    "correct_answer": "15 amps"
  },
  {
    "question": "Equipment grounding conductors of sizes 6 AWG and smaller shall be identified by a continuous green color or a continuous green color with one or more ______ stripes on the insulation or covering, except where bare?",
    "choices": ["Orange", "Blue", "Black", "Yellow"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3407.2.1",
    "correct_answer": "Yellow"
  },
  {
    "question": "The common point on a wye-connection in a polyphase system or midpoint on a single-phase, 3-wire system, or midpoint of a single-phase portion of a 3-phase delta system, or a midpoint of a 3-wire, direct-current system.",
    "choices": ["Neutral conductor", "Ground fault", "Neutral point", "Feeder"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 35",
    "correct_answer": "Neutral point"
  },
  {
    "question": "Conductors shall have a vertical clearance of not less than how many feet above roof surfaces?",
    "choices": ["8 ft", "5 ft", "6 ft", "4 ft"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3604.2.1",
    "correct_answer": "8 ft"
  },
  {
    "question": "Electrical services within the scope of the IRC are limited to ____-volt, 0-to ____- amp, single-phase systems.",
    "choices": ["120/240-volt, 200-amp", "120/240-volt, 150-amp", "120/208-volt, 400-amp", "120/240-volt, 400-amp"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3401.2",
    "correct_answer": "120/240-volt, 400-amp"
  },
  {
    "question": "Working space in front of panel boards shall not be less than what dimensions?",
    "choices": ["36 in by 30 in", "32 in by 28 in", "30 in by 30 in", "36 in by 36 in"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3405.2",
    "correct_answer": "36 in by 30 in"
  },
  {
    "question": "In clothes closets, surface mounted incandescent luminaires shall have how many inches clearance from the nearest point of storage space when mounted above a door?",
    "choices": ["10 in", "12 in", "15 in", "20 in"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 4003.12 (1)",
    "correct_answer": "12 in"
  },
  {
    "question": "The electrical chapters contained in the IRC (34 - 43) do not contain services rated over _____ amps?",
    "choices": ["200", "300", "400", "600"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3401.3",
    "correct_answer": "400"
  },
  {
    "question": "Conductors in NM cable assemblies shall be rated at ______ Celsius.",
    "choices": ["90 degrees Celsius", "50 degrees Celsius", "110 degrees Celsius", "100 degrees Celsius"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3705.4.4",
    "correct_answer": "90 degrees Celsius"
  },
  {
    "question": "In no case shall the point of attachment for service-drop conductors be less than how much above finish grade?",
    "choices": ["10 ft", "12 ft", "15 ft", "8 ft"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3604.3",
    "correct_answer": "10 ft"
  },
  {
    "question": "Over residential property and driveways, service-drop conductors shall have how many feet of clearance above final grade?",
    "choices": ["10 ft", "16 ft", "12 ft", "20 ft"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3604.2.2",
    "correct_answer": "12 ft"
  },
  {
    "question": "Underground wiring shall not be installed under or within the area extending 5 feet horizontally from the inside walls of pools?",
    "choices": ["True", "False"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 4203.8",
    "correct_answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Minimum of how many 20 amperes rated branch circuits shall be provided for receptacles located in the laundry area and shall serve only receptacle outlets in the laundry area?",
    "choices": ["2", "1", "3", "5"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3703.3",
    "correct_answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "A load where the maximum current is expected to continue for 3 hours or more.",
    "choices": ["Connected load", "Continuous load", "Intermittent load", "Feeder load"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 35",
    "correct_answer": "Continuous load"
  },
  {
    "question": "There shall be a wall switch at each floor to control stairway lighting where the stairway has ______ or more risers?",
    "choices": ["12", "20", "6", "9"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3903.3.1",
    "correct_answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "Service drop conductors less than 750 volts to ground shall have a clearance to the base of a diving platform no less than how many feet?",
    "choices": ["50", "25.5", "22.5", "20"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 4203.7",
    "correct_answer": "22.5"
  },
  {
    "question": "A luminaire facing upward on the bottom of a pool shall have the ______ adequately guarded to prevent contact by any person or shall be listed for use without a guard?",
    "choices": ["Lens", "Cover", "Enclosure", "Cage"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 4206.4.2",
    "correct_answer": "Lens"
  },
  {
    "question": "Electrical panel boards and overcurrent devices shall not be located in what kind of location?",
    "choices": ["Garages", "Clothes closets", "Outdoors", "Living rooms"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3405.5",
    "correct_answer": "Clothes closets"
  },
  {
    "question": "Receptacles shall be installed so that no point along the floor line in any wall space is more than how many feet, measured horizontally, from an outlet in that space?",
    "choices": ["5 ft", "6 ft", "3 ft", "2 ft"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3901.2.1",
    "correct_answer": "6 ft"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bonding shall be provided where necessary to ensure electrical ______ and the capacity to conduct safely any fault current likely to be imposed?",
    "choices": ["Fault path", "Grounding", "Discontinuity", "Continuity"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3609.1",
    "correct_answer": "Continuity"
  },
  {
    "question": "The markings for identification of electrical disconnection means and the associated hazards shall have the durability to withstand the ______ involved.",
    "choices": ["Weathering potential", "Installation", "Environment", "Wear potential"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3404.12 (1)",
    "correct_answer": "Environment"
  },
  {
    "question": "Flexible cords may be installed as a substitute for fixed wiring in a structure when installed in a dropped ceiling?",
    "choices": ["True", "False"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3909.1",
    "correct_answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "GFCI protection is required in which area?",
    "choices": ["Bathroom", "Bedroom", "Attic", "Living room"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3902.1",
    "correct_answer": "Bathroom"
  },
  {
    "question": "In calculating box fill, each 12 AWG conductor shall require how many cubic inches of free space within a box?",
    "choices": ["2 1/2 in", "2 1/4 in", "3 in", "1 3/4 in"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3905.12.2.1",
    "correct_answer": "2 1/4 in"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tamper proof receptacles are not required when a receptacle is located more than ______ feet above the floor?",
    "choices": ["3 ft", "5 ft", "5.5 ft", "6.5 ft"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 4002.14 Exception 1",
    "correct_answer": "5.5 ft"
  },
  {
    "question": "Receptacles that provide power for water-pump motors or other loads directly related to the circulation and sanitation system shall be permitted to be located at least ______ from the inside walls of pools?",
    "choices": ["6", "10", "15", "20"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 4203.1.1",
    "correct_answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rod and pipe electrodes serving as a grounding electrode shall not be less than how many feet in length?",
    "choices": ["6 ft", "8 ft", "5 ft", "9 ft"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3608.1.4",
    "correct_answer": "8 ft"
  },
  {
    "question": "A minimum of how many 20-ampere-rated branch circuits shall be provided to serve all wall and floor receptacle outlets located in kitchen, pantry, breakfast area, and dining areas?",
    "choices": ["2", "3", "1", "5"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3703.2",
    "correct_answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Constructed or protected so that exposure to a beating rain will not result in the entrance of water under specified test conditions.",
    "choices": ["Rain tight", "Rain proof", "Dead front", "Waterproof"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 35",
    "correct_answer": "Rain tight"
  },
  {
    "question": "Underground feeder cable specified as an allowable wiring method shall be designated as?",
    "choices": ["EMT", "RMC", "SE", "UF"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3801.2",
    "correct_answer": "UF"
  },
  {
    "question": "Interior metal water piping located more than how many feet from the point of entrance to the building shall not be used as part of the grounding electrode system?",
    "choices": ["3 ft", "4 ft", "5 ft", "6 ft"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3611.4",
    "correct_answer": "5 ft"
  },
  {
    "question": "All mechanical elements used to terminate a grounding electrode conductor or bonding jumper to the grounding electrodes shall be what when not buried or concrete encased?",
    "choices": ["Permanent", "Visible", "Lead-free", "Accessible"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3611.2",
    "correct_answer": "Accessible"
  },
  {
    "question": "An equipment grounding conductor shall not be used as a grounding electrode conductor?",
    "choices": ["True", "False"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3610.4",
    "correct_answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "A ______ minimum length of free conductor shall be provided at each outlet, junction, or switch plate for splicing or termination?",
    "choices": ["5 in", "3 in", "6 in", "4 in"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3406.11.3",
    "correct_answer": "6 in"
  },
  {
    "question": "Insulated conductors and cables exposed to direct rays of the sun shall be listed and labeled as what?",
    "choices": ["UV resistant", "Thermally coated", "Heat resistant", "Sunlight resistant"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3802.9",
    "correct_answer": "Sunlight resistant"
  },
  {
    "question": "Branch circuit conductors for fixed storage type water heaters having a capacity of 120 gallon or less shall be sized no less than ______ percent of the water heater rating?",
    "choices": ["100", "200", "150", "125"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3702.11 (1)",
    "correct_answer": "125"
  },
  {
    "question": "A minimum of how many 20-ampere branch circuits shall be provided to supply bathroom receptacle outlets?",
    "choices": ["2", "3", "1", "4"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3703.4",
    "correct_answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Except for Type IC luminaires, thermal insulation shall not be installed above a recessed luminaire or within how many inches of the recessed luminaire’s enclosure?",
    "choices": ["4 in", "6 in", "3 in", "2 in"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 4004.9",
    "correct_answer": "3 in"
  },
  {
    "question": "Nonmetallic boxes shall be used only with entirely nonmetallic sheaths, flexible cords and nonmetallic raceways?",
    "choices": ["True", "False"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3905.3",
    "correct_answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Service cables shall be supported by straps or other approved means within ______ of every service head, gooseneck or connection to a raceway or enclosure?",
    "choices": ["10 in", "12 in", "24 in", "36 in"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3605.7",
    "correct_answer": "12 in"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shall be the minimum burial depth of rigid metal conduit under a parking lot?",
    "choices": ["36 in", "24 in", "18 in", "12 in"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3803.1",
    "correct_answer": "24 in"
  },
  {
    "question": "Receptacles installed on 15 and 20 ampere rated branch circuits shall be of what type?",
    "choices": ["Arc-Fault", "Open", "Closed", "Grounding"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 4002.2",
    "correct_answer": "Grounding"
  },
  {
    "question": "For 15- and 20-amp branch circuits, the rating of any-one cord and plug connected piece of utilization equipment, not fastened in place, shall not exceed what percentage of the branch circuit ampere rating?",
    "choices": ["65%", "70%", "50%", "80%"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3702.4",
    "correct_answer": "80%"
  },
  {
    "question": "Connected to establish electrical continuity and conductivity is defined as what?",
    "choices": ["Grounding", "Bonding", "Jumping", "Interconnection"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 35",
    "correct_answer": "Bonding"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where a nonmetallic conduit is installed between a forming shell and a junction box, transformer enclosure, or other enclosure, a ______ AWG insulated copper bonding jumper shall be installed in this conduit except where a listed low-voltage lighting system not requiring grounding is used?",
    "choices": ["12", "6", "4", "8"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 4205.5",
    "correct_answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Kitchen countertop receptacles shall be installed so that no point along the wall line is more than how many inches from a receptacle?",
    "choices": ["12 in", "30 in", "24 in", "13 in"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3901.4.1",
    "correct_answer": "24 in"
  },
  {
    "question": "The earth shall not be considered as an effective ground-fault current path?",
    "choices": ["True", "False"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3908.5",
    "correct_answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "A branch circuit consisting of two or more ungrounded conductors having voltage difference between them, and a grounded conductor having equal voltage difference between it and each ungrounded conductor of the circuit, and that is connected to the neutral or grounded conductor of the system.",
    "choices": ["Branch circuit, multiwire", "Branch circuit, individual", "Branch circuit, appliance", "Branch circuit, general purpose"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 35",
    "correct_answer": "Branch circuit, multiwire"
  },
  {
    "question": "The only allowed disconnecting means for an air conditioning condensing unit shall be?",
    "choices": ["Switch within sight of the appliance", "Branch circuit overcurrent device", "Separable connector and receptacle", "Disconnect within sight of the unit"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 4101.5",
    "correct_answer": "Disconnect within sight of the unit"
  },
  {
    "question": "Copper conductors of 14 AWG in a 10-amp rated circuit shall have a maximum overcurrent protection device rating of what amperage?",
    "choices": ["14 amps", "12 amps", "20 amps", "10 amps"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3702.15 (1)",
    "correct_answer": "10 amps"
  },
  {
    "question": "Constructed or protected so that exposure to the weather will not interfere with successful operation.",
    "choices": ["Watertight", "Rain tight", "Rain proof", "Weatherproof"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 35",
    "correct_answer": "Weatherproof"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where subject to physical damage, direct buried conductors shall be protected by schedule 80 PVC rigid nonmetallic conduit or the equivalent?",
    "choices": ["True", "False"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 3803.3",
    "correct_answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Not readily accessible to persons unless special means for access are used.",
    "choices": ["Terminated", "Isolated", "Neutralized", "Separated"],
    "code_reference": "2024 IRC 35",
    "correct_answer": "Isolated"
  }
]